What'll it be?
Make it a strawberry sundae.
Sir...
This is a bar. It's no place for a kid.
Oh?
Then I'd expect to smell more alcohol,
but the smell of blood is
what's assaulting my nose here.
Well, that's fine with me...
What I'm interested in is
this strange rumor I heard.
They say that somewhere around
here there's some outdated, violent bar.
A place where they'll take
someone's life in place of money.
It's pretty scary.
Forgive me.
Royal Straight Flush, is it?
Laying a hand like that
will shorten a person's life.
How about I buy you a round!
Not bad, Mr. Royal Straight Flush.
The next time you open up shop,
don't forget to add
strawberry sundaes to the menu.
Bingo.
Yeah, my usual pizza.
The special mix with fresh ham
and garlic potatoes. Rush delivery.
What, my tab?
Don't sweat the small stuff.
Soon, I'll pay you in one
fell swoop for everything.
No olives. A large. Don't forget.
Are you listening to me, Dante?
Didn't you hear me? I'm studying.
I may be a man who does odd jobs,
but I have no desire to baby-sit some brat.
--Brat?
--Sorry, young lady.
In about 10 years or so,
I'll ask you out on a date.
And I'll tell you "no" in about 10 seconds.
Me, I'm into younger guys.
Listen, Dante. She may be a kid, but...
Oops... My apologies.
She is not just any girl.
She's Patty Lowell...
The Cinderella girl who is
heiress to the Lowell family fortune.
She sure doesn't look it.
That's because all this time she's
been living as an orphan downtown.
I see. Like Cinderella
after the magic wore off.
Actually, it's the opposite.
The other day, the head of
the Lowell family passed away.
When the will was read, an illegitimate
child came to light. The lucky winner was...
...our young lady, Patty?
Precisely. In other words,
the magic is just about to begin.
If you like, I could always
hire you as my servant...
Whatever.
Basically, it has been
requested that you escort Miss Patty
back to the Lowell Mansion
by 6:00pm tomorrow.
--That's all?
--That's all.
I won't do it. I've got a pizza on the way...
There's no pizza on the way.
I stopped by and talked with Andy
at the pizza place and told him
that until you pay your tab in full, they are
not to deliver a single pizza to you. Capisci?
You bastard. What right do you have to...
Shit... again?
If you win, I'll pay your
tab in full. And if you lose...
Fine, I got it.
Heads.
You're not much of a gambler, are you?
Shut up.
Dante.
You forget something?
You've got a show to play, right?
A show?
I'm counting on you.
I could come and see your show...
I mean, there must not be anyone
who comes to see you otherwise, right?
Sorry, but my shows are adults only.
So the woman in that picture is
coming to your show then, huh?
Picture?
Well, whatever you do, you
should buy yourself a new car.
I don't see any romance
happening in this car, that's for sure.
It's dirty, it stinks,
and it's falling apart.
Listen, when it comes to women, it's not
where you take them that's important.
It's how you get them there.
Dante.
This girl's life is mine!
Hey! Are you even listening to me?!
What are you doing?!
What was that all about?!
Don't you think that's a little
dangerous?! What if I died?
Can't you do something about this,
bro? You are a lawyer, aren't you?!
There's nothing that can be done!
If the person who sent that letter,
Patty Lowell, actually does exist,
the fortune belongs to her.
You're kidding me!
Take it easy, big bro.
If that letter isn't a fake,
then Patty Lowell will come here
around six o'clock tomorrow evening.
That's what I'm worried about!
Tomorrow at six in the evening...
That makes exactly one week, doesn't it?!
"If Patty Lowell's existence is proven
within one week of the death
of the Lowell family's head,
the entirety of the family
fortune is to go to her," eh?
Unbelievable... To think our ever-so-serious
other had an illegitimate child all this time...
Huh. So you can look pretty, too.
Is that a picture of some boy?
It's my mom!
And she's a lot prettier
than your girlfriend!
But... I don't remember anything about her...
My mom got sick and
died when I was just a baby.
That's what the director
of the orphanage said.
That's why I don't remember
anything about my mother...
The only thing I have is
this picture of her...
Wow! She's beautiful!
Is that a picture of your mother?
Hey, and you're pretty charming yourself!
Mind if I sit here?
Huh?
There are open seats all
over the place, aren't there?
--Here you go!
--Thank you!
I hope I am not bothering you.
It's no bother. But I can't
promise you that you'll live long.
What is that supposed to mean?!
Really!
Why would anyone need some
promise like that, just because they sit...
Good grief. That's why I told you...
He's dead.
Mom... Mom...
Looks like he was beaten to death.
It can't be! Was it you?!
Over here!
What is this?!
Hey, you. Why don't you
tell me what's going on?
Sure, how's this...
For the ten-odd seconds or so
that this train was in the tunnel,
in this car there were
those three, me and the girl.
And then our dead friend
here. That makes six.
First off, the old man. He didn't do it.
And the couple there
was making out in the dark.
You can see for yourself how the girl is.
That only leaves you...
No, there was one more person.
Or to be more precise, one more thing.
Who killed that guy?
Who knows...
It was a devil.
He was killed by a devil, wasn't he?
Could... Could a devil be hunting me, too?
Dante!
Let's go.
Checkmate.
Damn. I lost again!
Ever since we were kids, you've always
run out of steam in the closing stretch.
That's why Jenny left you.
It's because you got in the way!
No, that was because you were
at fault for jumping to conclusions.
Shit.
At any rate... You sure do
love that painting, don't you?
Yes. I guess it's because
looking at it puts me at peace.
I know, when we divide the fortune
among us, I'll take the artwork that's here.
Me, I'll take cold, hard cash.
Hey! Don't get ahead of yourselves!
We know. But we have to
be prepared for the worst...
That's all we're doing...
Welcome.
Give me your cheapest room.
I don't give a damn if it gets sun or not.
Because we'll be out of here
first thing in the morning anyhow.
One adult and one child.
She's not a child. She's a young lady.
What're you doing? Come on,
let's get to sleep right away.
--Mom.
--What?
Mom!
Mister!
Yes? What is it?
Where can I go to meet this woman?
Come on, your mother supposedly died, right?
Come on.
Shit. These beds really are small.
You, too. Get to bed.
Tomorrow's going to be an early day.
My mom... she didn't
actually get sick and die.
She disappeared.
I happened to overhear the director
of the orphanage talking about it.
My mom was being hunted by a devil.
And she didn't want me,
a baby, to be in danger,
so she put me in the care of the orphanage.
Is anyone hunted by a devil as good as dead?!
Is my mom dead?!
Am I going to be killed
by a devil too, then?!
Who knows...
Me, I don't care about
any fortune or inheritance...
If I were to get a little money,
I'd just want to use it to buy lots of
clothes and sweets and stuff like
that for the other kids at the orphanage.
But, clothes and sweets
aren't what they all want.
Like me, they just want to see
their mothers and their fathers!
More than anything.
You're probably just going to laugh at me...
Nope.
Everyone wants to see their parents.
Dante...
Well, sorry, but I've got a hot date
with some pretty girls in Sandman Land...
You get some sleep, too.
Okay.
Hey! Where's my daughter?!
Daughter?
The kid I checked in together with!
Hmmm... I don't know
what you're talking about, sir.
You bastard, what are you?
Me, I know pretty much all about you.
Yeah, then you know that thing
won't be enough to kill me, don't you?
So, where is Patty?
Okay, fine...
Well, you see, right now in the demon world,
the four most powerful
devils are vying for power.
Things are pretty dangerous.
Who told you to do this?
Huh?
Who told you to go after Patty?
It must be someone from the Lowell family...
Someone who doesn't want
Patty to claim the inheritance.
Sorry. I'm just one of their grunts.
They don't tell me anything.
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Mom! I wanted to see you so bad!
I'm sorry, Patty.
I won't do anything to
make you feel lonely again.
Mom!
Because you're about to die right now!
And your mom's going to kill you!
Hey there.
You're not actually into
lame operas like this, are you?
Dante!
Um... I was... my mom...
It looks like we're going to have to
wait a bit longer for the touching finale.
The show to come isn't for kids.
Miss... I'm sorry, but
now it's time for you to die.
It's because I was promised
I'd be rewarded if I killed you.
Get lost.
Time's up.
Brother, we did it! The fortune is ours!
This letter was just a bunch of nonsense.
You have a guest.
A guest?
Thank you.
And who might you be?
Oh my, that's not funny!
I'm Patty Lowell.
No! She's just a child!
That one's a fake.
I took every possible situation into account.
Luckily, I was able to find a girl
with the same name as me quite quickly.
I had it arranged so that all
attention would be on her.
Thanks to her, my trip
here was quite pleasant.
Well then. Why don't we just
hurry and deal with the formalities?
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid your
claim is invalid, Miss Patty Lowell.
Speaking as the lawyer,
I regret to inform you
that you have renounced your right to the
inheritance, as you missed the 6:00pm deadline.
Even if by just a second.
Really now! In his will, it says
within one week of his death.
I'm quite sure that my dad will have
been dead for exactly one week at 6:28.
And look! I am on time!
Will a driver's license
suffice for my identification?
No... It's no longer necessary.
What do you mean by that?
Because Patty Lowell's existence...
will never be confirmed!
--Brother?!
--And neither will yours!
The fortune is all mine!
And I'm not handing it over to anyone!
So it was you?
That requested I serve
as a bodyguard for Patty.
Did you think you were making some
small atonement for your sins against her?
You've got a pretty face, but
you're more terrible than those devils.
Damn, if you were a devil, I'd be able
to kill you without a second thought.
I need to work off some anger,
so I'm gonna let loose and unwind!
Guess I'll put on one hell of a big show!
I saw it all! The adults only part...
Wait!
Please wait. I'm begging you.
That child... Please let me care for her!
I want to do what I can to make amends...
So, is it all right that you're
not staying at the mansion?
It's fine. I received compensation.
Compensation?
Yep. Because I'm a little
girl who's been scarred
from being exposed to the
ugly world of adults.
I see.
And those clothes, are
those the "compensation"?
Yep. As well as clothes and sweets
for the kids at the orphanage.
In all, three truckloads!
That's great.
Ah, Morrison, you're here?
--Yeah.
--Huh?
I thought my strawberry sundae would be
delivered by the time I finished my shower...
That strawberry sundae?
That was my strawberry sundae!
Patty! What are you doing here?!
What... did you do to this room?
It was totally filthy and dorky, so I
cleaned it and did some cute decorating.
Yeah, but I'm more concerned
about my strawberry sundae...
That's what I charge for my work.
Thanks! It was so good!
What a pain... the only jobs I get
are those that don't pay anything.
My debt just keeps growing...
And now, I have to look
after some brat on top of it all.
On nights like tonight, I like to
open up the throttle on my motorcycle
and blow off some steam.
And if I should cross paths
with some devil along the way...
Well, that would
just make it perfect.